So, uh, Rohan-sensei?
Sorry to bother you with this, but I'd
like to ask for a favor if that's okay.
All right.
Let's hear it then.
Short version is, this spring, I
have some plans to travel abroad.
Do you now? Where to?
Uh, to Italy.
Italy? Yes!
Which brings me to my request.
Could you please use Heaven's
Door to make me fluent in Italian?
I'm going to need you to make a better
case for why I'd ever do any such thing.
Okay.
Truth is, I've never left the country
alone, and I feel extremely nervous.
So at the very least, I'd really like
to be able to speak the language.
Please help me out!
Bound for Italy, huh?
Perhaps you'd like to hear a
story about my own time there?
When we first met, I was
forced on a brief hiatus!
Due in no small part to a certain someone!
During that period of time, I
undertook some research for my work.
A journey which took me to Venice,
where I stayed for eight days.
And the story I discovered
was truly mind-boggling?
Very own ears its genre is horror
tell me do you know what a confessional
is the practice is found in all
italian churches and occurs in a set of
wooden booths the one with the curtains
is occupied by the parish priest
while the other is occupied by the
parishioner a small window connects their
respective booths, allowing them
to hear each other's voices.
However, at no point can they see
one another.
A very accommodating design, it enables
the parishioner to confess their sins
without ever revealing their identity.
The heart isn't built to
store secrets indefinitely.
After many years, it may break.
And the graver the secret, the
greater the strain it is forced
to endure.
Thus, a confessional provides a
means of relief for the heart.
Such was the
wisdom of its creators.
Though it was against the rules,
I captured some photos while the
priest wasn't around, to study the more
intricate details of its design later.
And, for the sake of the experience,
I thought I'd partake in
a confession of my own.
So, I entered at the booth, it would
surely help the authenticity of my work.
Father, I have come to confess.
I...
I've committed a great sin
I cannot bear to hold it in any longer.
Father.
I won't be able to sleep until I confess.
I swear to you,
at the time I did not
know the booth with the
curtains was actually
meant for the priest.
As a result, I suddenly found
myself receiving a confession.
It it was a great stroke of luck,
what is this great sin?
Wouldn't hurt to listen to the end.
Real experiences are
what yield great works,
it shouldn't matter who
hears the confession.
As long as this man continues
to believe I am the priest.
I imagine there shouldn't
be any harm done.
Father, is there something wrong?
No, it's nothing.
Please proceed.
Um, my child, I how should I begin?
It was
That evening.
Yes, all of this began
the evening of that day.
I was 24 years old at the time, and
made a modest living at a food market,
as a manual laborer.
I'd spend my days hauling sacks of corn
between the storehouse and the trucks.
It was hard work.
The job left me no time
for a personal life.
I was always working, and I hated it.
Then one day, sometime after 6 o 'clock,
as work carried on late like it always did,
From the corner of my eye, I
spotted a man approaching me.
The way he staggered, the emptiness in
his eyes, the stench that covered him.
I could tell at once, he was a vagrant.
I beg you, spare me some food, please sir.
He sounded pitiful,
and I caught him repeatedly stealing
glances at my meal on the table.
It made me swell with anger.
I thought to myself, how dare he?
I've been working like a dog all day while
he's been lazing around
in a park somewhere.
Yet he wants my food?
What a selfish bastard.
You know, whenever I get hungry, I go and
buy food with my own hard-earned money.
So why exactly can't you
do the same? Tell you what.
You put away all these sacks in
the storehouse, then I'll feed you.
I will work, sir. I promise.
But first, I'm begging you
to give me something to eat.
Please, I haven't eaten in five days.
It's the truth.
I just need a little something in the
tank, then I'll get right to it, I swear.
Please, sir.
That isn't how things work.
People only get paid after
they finish their job.
So, are you going to
start hauling or what?
Whoa there, pal!
What do you think you're
doing with that tiny one?
Your sacks are over here!
Big boy like you can
finish in an hour, right?
Because I want to go home already!
Too slow?
Pick up the pace!
Or did you decide you're
not that hungry after all?
Seriously, you lazy shit-smelling asswipe!
Hey, I'm doing you a favor by
whipping your ass into shape!
Oh, come on!
Do you actually think I'm gonna
fall for you playing dead?
I mean, who faints after
just ten minutes, huh?
You think I'm playing dead?
Why don't you take a closer look?
And then you can tell me again if
you still think I'm playing dead.
What the hell are you?
Let go of me!
What's wrong?
If you couldn't bear
the sight of me before,
why did you throw me even deeper
into this putrid sea of despair?
Mark my words, I will never
forget your face, ever!
I'll make sure to pay you back
properly for what you've done to me.
Wait for the happiest day of your life.
It will happen on the day you
cherish more than any other!
I'll come back to pay you a little
visit and take what I am owed.
My revenge!
Hey! Over here!
I think there's somebody
crushed underneath this sack.
He's dead.
Oh shit! You're right. He is.
Someone call a doctor!
No wait.
The police!
I didn't think he'd.
When he said he hadn't
eaten for five days.
I couldn't tell if he was lying.
Wait.
What did you say?
I don't think I heard you.
Right.
The vagrant spoke after he'd already died.
But how is such a thing possible?
Are you sure you didn't
dream this encounter?
Dream it?
Oh, how I wish it had been a dream.
But I'm afraid I've yet to
get to the terrifying part.
Father.
Following that incident, I
experienced an unnatural turn of luck.
First, I received inheritance money.
After that, I won the lottery.
I invested my winnings in real estate
and quickly made an incredible profit.
It was then that I came up with the
idea of producing corn-based snacks,
which all became instant worldwide
hits the second they hit the market.
And after having spent my life
as a bachelor, I got married.
My wife was a model who had once
graced the Milan Fashion Week stage.
My fortune was so vast I
hardly knew how to spend it.
At present, my estate is staffed
with 15 servants, three chauffeurs!
But my extreme success came with constant
anxiety lurking in the back of my mind.
Were thoughts of that dead
man and what he had said
still?
I eventually became a father.
A beautiful girl, just like her mother.
I want to show I'll show
you a super cool trick!
Don't blink, kay?
Aww, I missed!
Hey now, it's okay, you were so close!
You accidentally closed
your eyes at the end there.
Why don't you try again?
Okay!
As I stood there, watching my
daughter having fun in the piazza,
my worries faded, and I thought to
myself, Oh, what a happy man I am.
Just as I promised you.
Just as I promised you,
I've come back for a visit.
To give you what you deserve.
Young mistress, are you alright?
Shut your mouth!
It's fine.
Your daughter will get her
body back when we're done.
Please stop this.
Let go of me.
You're making a mistake.
I've never rocked you in any way.
Is that what you really think?
Bold thing to say to a
dead man after enjoying
a life filled with
everything you ever wanted.
Riches, renown, family. Am I right?
Tell me, did you truly believe
you got here all alone?
Without anyone secretly pulling
the strings from beyond?
huh? Yes,
I wanted you to be at your
peak before I struck you down,
if only to give you a small
taste of the despair you wrought on me.
But now, I'm not sure.
On the one hand, killing you is the
only thing that will bring me peace.
But on the other, it'd be a shame if you
died sincerely believing you were innocent,
and I'd hate to perpetuate
any more injustice.
That'd be the worst, wouldn't it?
So tell you what we're gonna do.
How's about we let fate decide whether or
not You deserve to die today that's right
you've still got a chance at life if the
heavens agree With you
that is if destiny takes
your side in my grudges
and deep baseless then
i'll spare your Miserable
life and disappear
and you'll never hear from me again nobody
could ask for a more Impartial judge now
wouldn't you agree well will you try your
luck or die where you
stand i i have No idea
what's going on about
you'll understand soon
now answer do you accept
these conditions or
Not why why is this happening to me speak
you idiot use that head
to think quickly or
else i'm Cutting it off yes i accept the
conditions what other
choice do i have good catch
Destiny can manifest in
ways we often overlook Look.
Throw a piece of popcorn
higher than that street
lamp and catch it in
your mouth as it falls.
Do it three times in a row.
If you succeed, destiny is on your
side and I'll disappear as promised.
A silly game is deciding my fate?
I'll remind you that my fate
will also be affected by this.
You better watch what
you call a silly game.
You'll throw as soon as I clap my hands.
If the popcorn doesn't fly high
enough or you take too long,
I'll kill you immediately.
So get ready, because we're
starting right now! No, wait!
Please give me a moment!
Up it goes, and clear!
But why?
Why am I being forced to do this?
I can see it falling!
I can't see!
No!
That was way too close,
but I actually did it!
I caught it!
That's one down!
It's time for round two.
Grab another piece of
popcorn and let's go!
No, no, wait, please!
The sun was in my eyes.
It completely blinded me!
We can just continue
this in the shade, right?
Next you'll ask for a juice
box and a pat on the head. Huh?
You'll throw the popcorn right
here, and you'll throw it right now!
Two more to go, hop to it, and
remember if you miss, you die.
And if you succeed, I'll disappear
without saying another word.
So, your second throw, now!
If I make all three, you swear
you'll disappear for good?
If that's what it'll take to
save my life, then so be it!
Enough talk!
Make your throw now or you're dead!
Alright, yeah!
This will be way easier
with the sun obscured!
I can see it coming straight down to me!
No!
Look at that! How cute!
All the little birdies
want to join the party!
Oh yeah!
Did you see me?
That there was the second one in the
can! Boom! That's right! I'm on a roll!
Man, I can't believe I thought
this was gonna be difficult,
but I'm getting the hang of it!
I can win!
Nothing can stop me now!
Feel free to celebrate
as much as your rotten
little heart desires
after we're actually done.
It's time for the final throw!
Go ahead, asshole!
Smack those hands together!
Just one more...
What the hell?
You're screaming rather loud for someone
who brought this down upon himself.
What did you think was going to happen when
you scattered that whole bag of popcorn?
Just look at your face!
This is it.
The last one.
If I throw it higher
than the street lamp...
You greedy bastards! Get out of here!
I'm all out!
There's nothing left!
It's time.
Make your last throw!
Ah! Wait! Just a second!
How's that?
Those stupid pigeons won't
go anywhere near the fire!
I oiled it up and lit it!
Worked like a freakin' charm!
Home stretch, baby!
Pack your bags and get ready to bounce!
Huh?
A flame!
Where did it go? Damn it!
The sunlight's completely engulfed it!
This is bad!
I can't see it! No! Where'd it go?
Destiny has spoken.
Looks like you did deserve
to lose your head after all.
You're wondering how I'm sitting
here, speaking with you right now,
aren't you, Father?
You see, it's the same
reason for my visit today.
I cannot bear it myself any longer,
that despicable sin I've committed.
The spirit of that vagrant,
he'd made me so rich that virtually
nothing was outside my grasp.
It took almost no effort to find a
servant who would do anything I commanded.
Master, come out of there, please.
Master, I've told you, no matter how many
times you confess, I will never leave you.
You who paid me off to surgically
discard my old face and take on yours,
only to throw me into the maw of such a
terrifying nightmare without
even a second thought.
I will never forgive you.
I will bear this grudge
till the end of time.
So you're able to follow
me even into the church?
Listen closely to my words.
The day which your sweet,
dear daughter cherishes
more than any other
will be the day that I
come to exact my revenge.
Can't let him out of your sight till then.
Otherwise, he'll just cook up
another one of those dirty tricks.
Wherever you may tread, we'll
be one step behind you always!
Whoa!
Now that's scary! Uh, Okuyasu?
And Yukako?
Yo, Rohan-sensei, was that really
a true story you just told us?
Excuse me, can I get a
thing of Baby tea over here?
When did you show up exactly?
and to so shamelessly accuse me of lying.
Hang on.
Nobody said you were lying.
I just think it's way more
likely that those spooky,
angry ghost things were stand users
rather than vengeful spirits or whatever,
you know?
Well, either way, they're
remarkably patient.
Man, I can't imagine having ghosts
haunt me for the rest of my life.
That's way too much.
Hey, Koichi, you'll have to tell me
right away if that ever happens to you.
I'll come banish the mean ghost
before it lays a finger on you.
Oh, thank you.
What's become of that man since?
I, Rohan Kishibe, have yet to discover.
I should give some thought
to paying him another visit.
Perhaps next year, or the year after.
He kept on walking, even with
those specters trailing him.
Alone, yet undeterred.
His may not have been a good heart,
but he is undeniably resilient.
And it might be that I am the only
one who thinks that about him.
I want to know the truth.
Of life that never melts.
To chain a mystic rise.
I'm coming.
I'm on my way to find.
Eternal varieties.
Expanding all their tears.
By the sun.
I can feel my heart beating.
I can see my faith all spinning.
Long beyond the dark.
Rise up to the sky like a butterfly.
Show me what's inside.
I don't know the world's cold.
Shining stars will guide me to.
Somewhere high.
Finding the truth.
Beyond the heaven's door.
Thank you.